[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gangster Al Capone, popular as Scarface, was known by what other nickname?", "correct_answer": "Snorky", "incorrect_answers": ["Loverboy", "The senator", "The fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the author of the 1988 book \u2018The Alchemist\u2019?", "correct_answer": "Paulo Coehlo", "incorrect_answers": ["J. K. Rowling", "Umberto Eco", "Terry Pratchett"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This battle represented the farthest Westward advance into Central Europe of the Ottoman Empire.", "correct_answer": "The Siege of Vienna, 1529", "incorrect_answers": ["The Conquest of Vlad, 1529", "The Battle of Greece, 1529", "The Battle of Belgrade, 1529"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the father of the fictional black cat Midnight Louie?", "correct_answer": "Three OClock Louie", "incorrect_answers": ["Louie Temple Barr", "Louis the LVII", "Noontime Louie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Liesls boyfriend who was Sixteen Going On Seventeen in the movie The Sound of Music?", "correct_answer": "Rolf", "incorrect_answers": ["Georg", "Hans", "Max"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements are wrong about the reproduction of the Tasmanian devil?", "correct_answer": "The female has six nipples", "incorrect_answers": ["The female gives birth to 20-30 young", "Gestation lasts 21 days", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actor who played the Scarecrow in 2005s Batman Begins originally auditioned for what part?", "correct_answer": "Batman", "incorrect_answers": ["Lucius Fox", "The Scarecrow", "A Person from the League of Darkness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What astronaut or cosmonaut performed the first space walk on March 18, 1965?", "correct_answer": "Leonov", "incorrect_answers": ["Glenn", "Aldrin", "Shepherd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning actress voiced Grendels Mother in the 2007 performance capture movie Beowulf?", "correct_answer": "Angelina Jolie", "incorrect_answers": ["Penelope Cruz", "Julia Roberts", "Halle Berry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following was invented by a woman?", "correct_answer": "all of these", "incorrect_answers": ["circular saw", "street-cleaning machine", "windshield wipers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the chestnut fruit, which is not actually a nut?", "correct_answer": "It is the only nut that contains vitamin C.", "incorrect_answers": ["Their starch content is equal to that of the potato.", "It contains bad cholesterol.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I ran into the bathroom and decided to brush my teeth. Upon looking up, I panicked due to my spectrophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Mirrors", "incorrect_answers": ["Pimples", "Uncombed hair", "Wearing no make-up"]}]